# COSTANDINO ELEFTHERIADIS

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

(+27) 83 262 5020

dinoelef@gmail.com

dinothedeveloper.github.io

in <u>dino-eleftheriadis</u>

Johannesburg, South Africa

# **KEY SKILLS**

- React
- Angular
- · JavaScript & TypeScript
- · HTML & CSS
- C#
- SQL
- Kubernetes
- Docker
- · Octopus Deploy
- SonarQube
- Azure
- Kibana

#### **EDUCATION**

Jan - Dec 2021 - 2021 ~ University of Pretoria

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY HONOURS IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS.

Jan - Dec 2018 - 2020 ~ IIE Varsity College Sandton

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER AND INFORMATION SCIENCES (Qualified with distinction).

# LANGUAGE

English: Fluent (Read, Write and Speak) Greek: Satisfactory (Speak and Read) Afrikaans: Satisfactory (Read and Write)

#### NATIONALITY

South African
Greek (EU Passport & Citizenship)

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a software engineer with two years of working experience. I possess an innate passion for continuous learning, unparalleled teamwork abilities, and a proven history of consistently delivering exceptional outcomes. I approach tasks with meticulous organisation and unwavering motivation, striving to achieve optimal results. Moreover, my remarkable entrepreneurial spirit and determination drive me to actively contribute to the growth and development of businesses.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Web Developer & UX Specialist

June - Present 2023 - Present

Bettabets

• As the Lead Frontend Developer and UX Specialist at Bettabets, I've transformed the online casino to a whole new level, creating an eye-catching and intuitive user experience. Through the use of A/B testing, heatmaps, user recordings, and other data analytics, I've optimized functionality and engagement as well as leading a major increase in efficiency. My innovative approach has not only revamped the platform but also positioned Bettabets as a leader in online casino design, showcasing my prowess in frontend development and UX enhancement.

# **Co-Founder and Software Engineer**

Jan - June 2023 - 2023

MetaFushko Inc

- I was a co-founder of MetaFushko Inc., a blockchain company that developed smart contracts, cryptocurrencies, NFTs, and web3 gaming services. As part of my role, I actively contributed to coding and development as well as being responsible for managing, running the project build and leading a team of developers, 3D and 2D artists, and marketers.
- MetaFushko Inc. initially began with a humble duo, and it since flourished into a cohesive team of ten colleagues.

# **Junior Software Engineer**

Paycorp payment services

Jan - Jan 2022 - 2023

- I took on an early role as a team-lead and managed various developers below
  me. In my role, I exhibited excellent communication skills, goal-setting, strategyplanning, and organisational skills. I worked on developing a web application
  that assisted the finance department to monitor and pay merchants who own
  self-cashing ATMs. I also worked on smaller projects for other departments
  within the company.
- I maintained frequent and meaningful interactions with the group Chief Information Officer and other esteemed senior leaders within the organisation.
   Additionally, I took on the responsibility of delivering regular presentations to these executives, and providing comprehensive project updates.

### **Freelance Developer**

Jan - Jan 2022 - 2023

I worked as a website developer on a freelance basis. During my time as a
freelance developer, I worked with clients to establish project requirements,
target audiences, and identify solutions to any issues encountered so as to
create the best website solution for the client base.